<_>
   <form_key>wlj8E8J4D3RVQK34</form_key>
   <name>Noble_Extended_Order_Grid</name>
   <channel>community</channel>
   <version_ids>
      <version_ids>2</version_ids>
   </version_ids>
   <summary>This Magento extension gives the user the flexibility to customize the orders grid in the admin.</summary>
   <description>Noble Extended Order Grid
Features Turn off any of the default columns with a simple Yes/No Add new custom columns Available custom columns are: Shipping method Payment method Shipping country, Shipping Region, Shipping City, Shipping Postcode, Billing country , Billing Region, Billing City, Billing Postcode, Customer email Amount of items in the order Subtotal Customer Group Implementation Simply upload the files in the app folder to the app folder of your Magento installation. It is recommended to test this on a test server first. The current module has only been tested with Magento Community 1.7 Usually you will be required to log out and log back in in order for it to work. Configuration Configuring the columns is very easy. Just login to your Magento Admin panel, go to Configuration. And on the left choose the &quot;Extended Order Grid&quot; link in the &quot;Noble Extensions&quot; section. More information on github: https://github.com/KingIsulgard/Magento-Noble-Extended-Order-Grid</description>
   <license>GPL</license>
   <license_uri>https://github.com/KingIsulgard/Magento-Noble-Extended-Order-Grid/blob/master/license.md</license_uri>
   <version>1.0.1</version>
   <stability>stable</stability>
   <notes>Added Shipping Region, Shipping CIty, Shipping Postcode, Billing Region, Billing CIty, Billing Postocde as extended custom columns. Also now you can choose to display countries either as the country code or the full country name.</notes>
   <authors>
      <name>
         <name>Gilles Lesire</name>
      </name>
      <user>
         <user>NobleHouse</user>
      </user>
      <email>
         <email>gilles.lesire@gmail.com</email>
      </email>
   </authors>
   <depends_php_min>4.0.0</depends_php_min>
   <depends_php_max>6.0.0</depends_php_max>
   <depends>
      <package>
         <name>
            <name/>
         </name>
         <channel>
            <channel/>
         </channel>
         <min>
            <min/>
         </min>
         <max>
            <max/>
         </max>
         <files>
            <files>  </files>
         </files>
      </package>
      <extension>
         <name>
            <name>Core</name>
         </name>
         <min>
            <min/>
         </min>
         <max>
            <max/>
         </max>
      </extension>
   </depends>
   <contents>
      <target>
         <target>magelocal</target>
         <target>magecommunity</target>
         <target>mageetc</target>
      </target>
      <path>
         <path/>
         <path>Noble</path>
         <path>modules/Noble_AdminOrderGrid.xml</path>
      </path>
      <type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>file</type>
      </type>
      <include>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
      </include>
      <ignore>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
      </ignore>
   </contents>
</_>
